saavn.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Saavn

Last Updated: Nov 21, 2018

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through the web site located at [JioSaavn.com](http://www.jiosaavn.com/) and our JioSaavn application (collectively, the web site and the app shall be referred to as the "Platform"); whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology. The Platform is offered by Saavn Media Pvt. Ltd, who is the data controller ("JioSaavn", "we", "us", "our").

This Privacy Policy explains what information may be collected through the Platform, how such information may be used and/or shared with others, how we safeguard it and how you may access and control its use in connection with our marketing communications and business activities.

### Quick Guide to Contents

### Special Message for European Users

As you are probably aware, a new European law called the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR") gives certain rights to European users in relation to their personal data. For that reason, we have implemented additional access and transparency controls to allow our European users to take advantage of the rights afforded to them under the GDPR. If you are a European user of the Platform, you can better understand these rights here.

### Information We Collect

#### Information You Give Us

When you use the Platform, for example to register to create an account, update your information, sign up for a subscription, use certain features, access or download content, purchase items or enter into promotions, refer others to the Platform, interact with us via third party application or social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us, we or our service providers or business partners may collect information that relates to you, including personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, mobile phone number, credit card or debit card details, geographic location, mailing address, date of birth, gender, demographic information, photos, videos, and social media account details.

Click here to learn more about the legal reasons (Contract and Legitimate Interest) why JioSaavn may collect this information under the GDPR.

#### Information Collected Automatically

Whenever you visit or interact with the Platform, JioSaavn, as well as any third-party advertisers and/or service providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the Platform is accessed and used ("Usage Information"). Usage Information may include information collected in the following ways:

  * **_Log Files:_** Information is logged about your use of the Platforms, including your browser type, operating system, activations, content you purchase, access, download or burn, access and listening times, the page served and the preceding page views. This statistical usage data provides us with information about the use of the Platform, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Platform, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they "click" on.

It also provides us with information about your interactions with songs, playlists, audiovisual content and other JioSaavn users, as well as advertising and products or services offered through or linked from the Platform.

This information helps us keep our Platform fresh and interesting to our visitors and tailor content to a visitor’s interests.

Click here to learn more about the legal reasons (Consent, Contract, and Legitimate Interest) why JioSaavn may collect this information under the GDPR.

  * **_Location Information:_** We may collect information about the location of your device when you access or use the Platform; or if you choose to turn on your Bluetooth, Wi-Fi or other geolocation functionality when you use the App, subject to your consent, the App may collect and use your geolocation information.

We may share your location with certain third-parties for analytics and advertising purposes.

If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you can subsequently stop the collection of this information at any time by going to the setting feature on your Device and changing your preferences. If you do so, certain features of our App may no longer function. You also may stop our collection of location information by following the standard uninstall process to remove our App from your device.

Click here to learn more about the legal basis (Consent) for which JioSaavn may collect this information under the GDPR.

  * **_Device Identifiers:_** JioSaavn may automatically collect your IP address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for the computer, mobile device, tablet or other device (collectively, "Device") you use to access the Platform, including the hardware model and mobile network information. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device when you access a web site or its servers, and includes AD-IDs or IDFAs, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier.

Click here to learn more about the legal bases (Consent, Contract, and Legitimate Interest) for which JioSaavn may collect this information under the GDPR.

#### Information Received from Other Sources

We also may obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through the Platform. This includes:

  * Social media and interactive services you may choose to connect with
  * Third party applications and sites you may choose to integrate
  * JioSaavn's partners and service providers

Click here to learn more about the legal reasons (Consent, Contract, and Legitimate Interest) for which JioSaavn may collect this information under the GDPR.

  * **_Social Media and Interactive Services:_** If you create an account using your credentials from a third-party social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, profile and account information, such as lists of your friends, "likes", comments you have shared, groups and location, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such third-party social media site. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on our Platform to your profile page to share with others within your network.

In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party application or website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections'" web page, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service.

  * **_Information We Receive from You and/or Your Telecom Provider:_** If you choose to create and/or log in to a JioSaavn account using your SIM credentials through a single-sign-on mechanism, you acknowledge and agree that we will have access to the following information that you may provide and/or hereby consent to be collected from your telecom service provider: mobile number, age range, gender, and unique Jio subscriber ID.

  * **_Integrating Third Party Applications and Sites:_** You may integrate your JioSaavn account with third party applications and sites. If you do, we may receive similar information related to your interactions with the JioSaavn service on third party application(s) you have chosen to integrate with JioSaavn, as well as information about your publicly available activity on the third party application or site.

  * **_JioSaavn's Partners and Service Providers:_** We may also receive information about you from our partners and service providers, (including, for example, business partners, analytics vendors, advertising networks and search information providers) which we use to personalize your JioSaavn experience, to measure ad quality and responses, and to display ads that are more likely to be relevant to you.

  * **_Information We Receive from the Predecessor Application:_** We may also receive/migrate certain information about you from a previous version or predecessor application that you may migrate and/or upgrade from, to help personalize your JioSaavn experience.

### How We Use the Information Collected

We use the information about you to operate and maintain our Platform, and provide you with access to the Platform, including providing customer and technical support, processing payments and transactions, and tailoring content and advertising. JioSaavn will use your information to:

  * respond to your questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * provide you with access to certain features of the Platform; 
  * deliver the services you request, process transactions and send you related information;
  * verify your identity; communicate with you about your activities on the Platform;
  * tailor content, advertisements, offers and promotions offered by JioSaavn and others, and provide news and other information we think will be of interest to you;
  * perform market research, Platform analytics and operations;
  * personalize and improve the Platform and products, services and advertising (including for third party products and services) made available on or outside the Platform (including on other sites/ apps that you visit), for example by providing personalized or localized content, recommendations, features, and provide advertisements, content or features that match your interests and preferences;
  * link or combine with information we receive from others to help understand your needs and to provide you with better service;
  * contact you with regard to your use of the Platform and interest in certain products and services, and, in our discretion, changes to any JioSaavn policy;
  * communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, for marketing and promotional purposes via emails, notifications, or other messages, consistent with any permissions you may have communicated to us; and
  * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your personal information (relevant to those purposes) or otherwise with your consent.

We may also use Device Identifiers to administer the Platform, help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze trends, track users’ web page movements, help identify, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Cookies

Our Platform uses cookies (data files placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Platform)and/or other similar technologies such as [device-IDs], [in-App codes], mobile analytics software, pixel tags or web beacons (a transparent graphic image, sometimes called a web beacon or tracking beacon, placed on a web page or in an email, which indicates that a page or email has been viewed and may tell your browser to get content from another server) to collect and store certain information. These typically involve pieces of information or code that a website transfers to or accesses from your computer hard drive or mobile device to store and sometimes track information about you.

Cookies and similar technologies enable you to be remembered when using that computer or device to interact with websites and online services and can be used to manage a range of features and content as well as storing searches and presenting personalised content.

Our platform uses cookies and similar technologies to:

  * to distinguish you from other users of our Platform and to facilitate site navigation,
  * to associate you with social networking sites and, if you so choose, enable interaction between your activities on the Platform and your activities on such social networking sites,
  * to personalize your experience while visiting our Platform (such as allowing us to select which content, ads or offers are most likely to appeal to you, based on your interests, preferences, location, or demographic information), including personalizing content from the providers of goods and services that you may be able to purchase through the Platform or otherwise (who may pay us to show you such content) · Find Out More
  * to collect information enabling digital rights management, and
  * for security purposes.

This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you use our Platform and also allows us to improve our Platform. Similarly, we may use analytics platforms and other tracking technologies to help us track and analyze usage of our Platform, using cookies, pixels and other tracking technologies.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies and similar technologies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that and your help screen or manual will tell you how to do this. We also give you information about how to disable cookies here. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our website if you do so.

A number of cookies and similar technologies we use last only for the duration of your web or app session and expire when you close your browser/or exit the App. Others are used to remember you when you return to the Platform and will last for longer.

Click here to learn more about the legal reasons (Consent, Contract and Legitimate Interest) for which JioSaavn may collect this information under the GDPR.

#### Your Choices

We use cookies and/or other similar technologies , such as tracking GIFs, web beacons pixel codes and in-app IDs, either alone or in combination with each other, to create a unique device ID.

We use the following types of cookies:

  * **Strictly necessary** cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website and under our terms with you. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
  * **Analytical/performance** cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us for our legitimate interests of improving the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
  * **Functionality** cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us, subject to your choices and preferences, to personalise our content, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
  * **Targeting/Advertising** cookies. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information subject to your choices and preferences to make our website/App and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

For more information on advertising, please see the section on Advertising Services.

We may also work with advertising networks that gather information about the content on our Platform you visit and on information on other websites and services you visit. This may result in you seeing advertisements through our Platform for us and for third parties, as well as seeing our advertisements when you visit other websites and services of third parties. For more information about interest-based advertising and how to turn this feature off see below or visit:

  * European users can also visit youronlinechoices.eu to learn how to opt out of having their data used for online behavioral advertising by European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) member companies.
  * Canadian users can also visit: youradchoices.ca/choices.
  * US users can visit Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) AppChoices [boutads.info/appchoices](http://aboutads.info/appchoices) and [boutads.info/choices](http://aboutads.info/choices) or [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/);
  * To opt out from the use of information about your online activities for online behavioral advertising by NAI member companies, visit [networkadvertising.org/choices](http://networkadvertising.org/choices).

Some browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, so note that our systems are not configured to recognize Do Not Track headers or signals from some or all browsers.

#### Disabling Cookies

The effect of disabling cookies depends on which cookies you disable but, in general, the website may not operate properly if all cookies are switched off. If you do disable or opt out of receiving cookies, please be aware that some features and services on our Platform may not work properly because we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your account(s). In addition, the offers we provide when you visit us may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests. If you only disable third party cookies, you will not be prevented from making purchases on our Platform. If you disable all cookies, you will be unable to complete a purchase on our Platform.

If you want to disable cookies on our site, you need to change your website browser settings to reject cookies. How you can do this will depend on the browser you use. You can also learn more about cookies by visiting [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) which includes additional useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browser. To delete or disable flash cookies, please visit [Adobe](http://www.adobe.com/) for more information.

Further details on how to disable cookies for the most popular browsers are set out below:

##### Microsoft Internet Explorer

  1. Choose Tools > Internet Options
  2. Click on the "Privacy" tab
  3. Select the appropriate setting

##### Google Chrome

  1. Choose Settings > Advanced
  2. Under "Privacy and Security", click "Content Settings"
  3. Click "Cookies"

##### Safari

  1. Choose Preferences > Privacy
  2. Click on "Remove all Website Data"

##### Mozilla Firefox

  1. Choose Tools > Options
  2. Click on the "Privacy" icon
  3. Find the "Cookie" menu and select the relevant options

Where you have not set your permissions, we may also separately prompt you regarding our use of cookies on the Site. Except for essential cookies, all cookies used on our site will expire as specified in the **Cookie Table** below. You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them here:

Cookie | Lawful Basis | Purpose | Expiration | Platform  
---|---|---|---|---  
P | Strictly Necessary | Subscription status. | Session | App  
L | Functionality | Used for identifying user's language. | 20 years | App  
geo | Functionality | Used for storing user's location. | 7 days | App  
I | Strictly Necessary | An encrypted cookie that stores user data like username, uid, firstname, lastname, email, phone number, network, access token, fbid. | 2 years | App  
B | Functionality | Uniquely identifies the browser of the user. | Jan 1, 2023 | App  
FBM_REFERER | Targeting / Advertising | Identifies if the user came from Facebook. |  | App  
device_id | Functionality | Identifies the device of the user. | 20 years | App  
CH | Targeting / Advertising | Identifies cohorts to which the user belongs. Used for targeting features and ads. | 1 day | App  
ATC | Strictly Necessary | Used as a security measure for preventing media downloading from site network. Identifies whether the user account is Facebook, phone, and/or email connected. | Session | App  
CHE | Functionality | Stores encrypted carrier name and phone number to fetch phone numbers directly from partner carriers. | Session | App  
latlong | Functionality | Used for storing the lat long of the user if explicitly provided | 20 years | App  
LO | Functionality | Stores whether to show language options or not. | 2 years | App  
SQ | Functionality | Stores the current state of the app sidebar. _No longer in use._ | 30 days | App  
exp_details | Functionality | Stores details about general A/B test experiments. | 30 days | App  
abpc | Functionality | Stores A/B test details and status of paywall. | 1 day | App  
BN | Targeting / Advertising | Stores bucket name for AB Tests. _No longer in use._ | 30 days | App  
fbsr_ | Functionality | _Set by Facebook_  
[More Info](https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings) | 20 years | App  
fbs_ |  | _Set by Facebook_  
[More Info](https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings) |  | App  
ssid | Functionality | Stores device id and session start time. | 20 years | App  
song_count | Functionality | Stores the number of times user has played songs in a given day. | 30 days | Mobile Web  
HW | Functionality | Stores height and width of the mobile view, for matching devices across sessions. | 30 days | Mobile Web  
ctx_logging | Functionality | Stores parameters for data logging. | 30 days | Mobile Web  
bottom_banner | Functionality | Used for deciding whether or not to show bottom banner. | 30 days | Mobile Web  
  
### Advertising Services

We may allow third parties to serve you ads across the Internet and use third party ad networks providers to help present ads on the Platform using Cookies and similar technologies/. These third parties may collect or have access to your Usage Information. In order to personalize these ads or content, we or a data partner may connect and/or share de-identified demographic or other data about you (received from third parties) either to data you provided to us or to Usage Information collected from you. The use of cookies, pixel tags, or similar technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies.

If you do not want to receive the benefits of targeted advertising, go the section below on Your Choices for more information on how to opt-out of these tracking and advertising services.

Please note that even after opting out of targeted advertising, you will still see advertisements while you’re browsing online, however they will not be targeted and may be less relevant to you and your interests, and we may still track your visits to the Platform for our own analytics, operations and security purposes.

#### More Information

Many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have compiled from your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted advertisements you may receive.

Please note that if a third party content provider asks us to show content to users with certain characteristics (for example, women ages 18-24) or a segment of that group (for example, women ages 18-24 who are located in a particular locality) and you respond to that content or click on links embedded in that content, the third-party content provider may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience that they are trying to reach.

JioSaavn does not have access to or control over cookies, web beacons, or other technologies that third parties who have asked us to show you content may use, and the privacy practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy. Please contact these companies directly for information on their data collection and privacy practices.

### Legal Bases

#### Contract

We may process your data if doing so is necessary to enter into or perform our contract with you – this is the agreement between us and you about the use of our Platform.

#### Legitimate Interests

We may process your data in our legitimate interests (where we have considered that these are not overridden by your rights), which we explain in more detail where mentioned in this policy. Our legitimate interests include improving our Platform to keep it fresh and interesting to our visitors, and ensuring that it is working well.

#### Consent

We may process your data with your consent, for example where we would like to share news about exciting features, new options, or other promotional and marketing content. Where we are processing your data based on your consent, you can withdraw your consent to that processing at any time by contacting us at [privacy@jiosaavn.com](mailto:privacy@jiosaavn.com).

#### Legal Requirement

We may process your data to comply with applicable laws and in cooperation with local law enforcement (for example, in some fraud prevention cases).

### Sharing of Information

The information collected or generated through your use of the Platform may be shared by you or by us as described below.

#### Sharing of Information by You

JioSaavn is a social service that offers many ways to find, enjoy, and share content. Your name and/or username, profile picture, who you follow, your followers, and your JioSaavn user profile will be publicly available.

##### Your Activities

Your activity on the Platform (e.g., music you listen to, music you share), playlists created or followed, and content you post to the Platform are made publicly available by default and can be accessed by users who follow you or view your JioSaavn profile.

Your activity will also be displayed publicly in third-party search engine results and may appear together with other public profile information, such as your playlists, picture and name and/or username. _The information associated with you that is made publically available (such as your photo or user name) depends on your login method. For example, if you do not want your photo to be made publically available in connection with to your email address, you can login by phone or email._

We describe the controls that you can use to limit the sharing of your information in the Your Choices section.

##### Third Party Platforms

If your JioSaavn account is connected to a third party application or social media platform, JioSaavn may automatically share your activity with that service, including the content you use and such information may be attributed to your account on the third party platform and published on such service.

Likewise, if you log into a third party application with your JioSaavn account, that third party application may have access to certain information such as your JioSaavn playlists and activity.

A third party platform’s use of information collected from you (or as authorized by you) is governed by the third party platform’s privacy policies and your settings on the relevant service.

#### Sharing of Information by Us

We may share aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and Usage Information with third parties. We may also share your information as disclosed at the time you provide your information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy and in the following circumstances:

##### Third Parties

In order to carry out your requests, to make various features, services and materials available to you through the Platform, and to respond to your inquiries, we may share your information with third parties that perform functions on our behalf, such as companies that host or operate our Platform; payment processors; analyze data; provide customer service; sponsors or other third parties that participate in or administer our promotions.

Your information may also be used by us or shared with our sponsors, partners, advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies or other third parties in connection with marketing, promotional, and other offers, as well as product information, and for such third party’s advertising, analytics and market research.

These advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies use various technologies to collect data in order to send (or serve) relevant ads to users on our Platforms, or on platforms or websites operated by third parties. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of various technologies by advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies. Please see the Cookies section for further information.

We may also share your information with the rights holders that license content to JioSaavn to stream on the Platform.

##### Your Agreement To Have Your Personal Information Shared

While on our Platform, you may have the opportunity to opt-in to receive information and/or marketing offers from someone else or to otherwise consent to the sharing of your information with a third party. If you use the social sharing features of the Platform, your information may be shared with certain of your friends or groups. If you agree to have your information shared, your information will be disclosed to the third party and the information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of that third party.

##### Business Transfers

Your information may also be used by us or shared with our subsidiaries and affiliates for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes. As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all or substantially all of our assets, or assets related to the Platform, your information may be disclosed to such entity as part of the due diligence process and will be transferred to such entity as one of the transferred assets.

Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.

##### Legal Disclosure:

JioSaavn may transfer and disclose your information to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce our Terms of Use or other applicable policies; to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, visitors to our Platform or the public.

#### Data Sharing and Communications

You may always direct us not to share your personal information with third parties, not to use your information to provide you with information or offers, or not to send you newsletters, e-mails or other communications by sending us an email at [privacy@jiosaavn.com](mailto:privacy@jiosaavn.com) or contacting us by mail at:

**JioSaavn – Attn: Legal**  
460 Park Avenue South, 4th Floor  
New York, NY 10016

Following the removal instructions in the communication that you receive. Your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date on which we receive it.

Please note that if you opt-out of various uses of your information the service we provide to you and relevant offers may be impacted. Also, if you opt out of receiving promotional offers, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

##### Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at [privacy@jiosaavn.com](mailto:privacy@jiosaavn.com). It is important to note that that this opt-out request does not prohibit us from sending you important administrative disclosures for non-marketing purposes. We will comply with your request as soon as is reasonably practicable.

### Your Rights

If you wish to verify, correct, or update any of your personal information collected through the Platform, you may contact us at the above address or e-mail.

In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain personal information you have submitted through the Platform. We are under no obligation to store such personal information indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such personal information.

In addition, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons.

You may have certain rights in relation to your personal information depending on your local laws. If you are in the EU, you have the right under certain circumstances:

  * to be provided with a copy of your personal data held by us;
  * to request the rectification or erasure of your personal data held by us;
  * to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data (while we verify or investigate your concerns with this information, for example);
  * to object to the further processing of your personal data, including the right to object to marketing (as mentioned in Advertising Services section;
  * to request that your provided personal data be moved to a third party.

You may opt out at any time from allowing further access by us to your location data by managing your preferences in your device settings. You can also stop all information collection by un-installing the App. You may use the standard un-install processes as may be available for your mobile device.

Your right to withdraw consent where the processing of your personal information by us is based on consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent without detriment at any time by contacting us ]. You can also change your marketing preferences at any time.

You can also exercise the rights listed above at any time by contacting us at [privacy@jiosaavn.com](mailto:privacy@jiosaavn.com) Privacy Officer's email address or other email contact].

If your request or concern is not satisfactorily resolved by us, you may approach your local data protection authority, (see <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.html>).

The Information Commissioner is the supervisory authority in the UK and can provide further information about your rights and our obligations in relation to your personal data, as well as deal with any complaints that you have about our processing of your personal data.

### Children

The Platform is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we determine upon collection that a user is under this age, we will not use or maintain his/her personal information without the parent/guardian’s consent.

### Security of your Information

We use certain reasonable security measures to help protect your personal information. However, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use the Platform and provide us with your information at your own risk.

### Other Sites

The Platform may contain links to other sites that we do not own or operate. This includes links from service providers, advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo(s) as part of a co-branding agreement. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these sites or their content, products, services or privacy policies or practices. These other web sites may send their own cookies to your Device, they may independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. You should also independently assess the authenticity of any site which appears or claims that it is one of our Platforms (including those linked to through an email or social networking page).

### International Transfers

JioSaavn is a global business headquartered in the United States. JioSaavn processes, transfers and stores information about its users on servers located in the United States, India and Singapore. As a result, JioSaavn may transfer your information with third parties located in countries other than your home country. Your personal information may therefore be subject to privacy laws that are different from those in your country of residence.

If you are located in India, the European Economic Area (“EEA”), Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect may be transferred to and processed by third parties in a country outside of your country of residence.

Where your information is transferred outside the EEA, we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is subject to appropriate safeguards, such as relying on a recognised legal adequacy mechanism, and that it is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

We may transfer your personal information outside the EEA:

  * in order to store it;
  * in order to enable us to provide goods or services to you and fulfil our contract with you. This includes order fulfilment, processing of payment details, and the provision of support services;
  * where we are legally required to do so;
  * in order to facilitate the operation of our group of businesses, where it is in our legitimate interests and we have concluded these are not overridden by your rights.

Where your personal data is transferred outside the EEA we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that this data is subject to appropriate and required safeguards. Some non-EEA countries are recognized by the European Commission as having an “adequate” level of data protection according to the standards set by the European Commission. For a list of these non-EAA countries with adequate safeguards and how the European Commission came to this determination click [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en).

For data transfers from the EEA to non-EEA countries that are _not_ considered to have adequate data protection measures, JioSaavn has instituted other legal and contractual measures to protect your personal data. In particular, JioSaavn requires that the non-EEA recipient be bound by the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses to protect your personal data. To obtain a copy of these Standard Contractual Clauses please click [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries_en).

### Changes

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page and, in relation to substantive changes, will be notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or consent to these updates or changes, do not continue to use the Platform.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

**JioSaavn – Attn: Legal**  
Address: 460 Park Avenue South, 4th Floor, New York, NY 10016  
Re: JioSaavn Privacy Policy

E-Mail: [privacy@jiosaavn.com](mailto:privacy@jiosaavn.com)
